Guide to the Duke Endowment Archives, 1902-2018 and undated, bulk 1925-2006 RL.00332
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Rural Church Division Series (RESTRICTED), 1918-2006 and undated, 152 boxes
  - Building Grant Files Subseries, 1920-2006 and undated
    - Bethesda Church, Durham County, 1961, 1972, 2 folders (Box RCD 30)
    - Bethesda Church, Gaston County, 1934-1967, 1982-1984, 2 folders (Box RCD 30)
    - Bethesda Church, Robeson County, 1926-1936, 1975-1981, 3 folders (Box RCD 30)
    - Bethesda Church, Stanley County, 1962 (Box RCD 30)
    - Bethesda Church, Stokes County, 1959-1962 (Box RCD 30)
    - Bethlehem Church, Burke County, 1931-1955 (Box RCD 30)
    - Bethlehem Church, Cabarrus County, 1958-1959 (Box RCD 30)
    - Bethlehem Church, Carteret County, 1940-1950 (Box RCD 30)
    - Bethlehem Church, Catawba County, 1929-1951, 2 folders (Box RCD 31)
    - Bethlehem Church, Davidson County, 1977-1978 (Box RCD 31)
    - Bethlehem Church, Davie County, 1958-1959 (Box RCD 31)
    - Bethlehem Church, Forsyth County, 1934-1936 (Box RCD 31)
    - Bethlehem Church, Guilford County, 1952-1953, 1987-1988, 2 folders (Box RCD 31)
    - Bethlehem Church, Iredell County, 1961, 1965-1972, 3 folders (Box RCD 31)
    - Bethlehem Church, Lee County, 1958 (Box RCD 31)
    - Bethlehem Church, Lincoln County, 1929-1949 (Box RCD 31)
    - Bethlehem Church, Mitchell County, 1955 (Box RCD 31)
    - Bethlehem Church, Pitt County, 1948-1965, 2 folders (Box RCD 31)
    - Bethlehem Church, Polk County, 1948-1950 (Box RCD 31)
    - Bethlehem Church, Rockingham County, 1940-1969, 1976-1980, 2 folders (Box RCD 31)
    - Bethlehem Church, Union County, 1935-1962, 1978-1982, 3 folders (Box RCD 31)
    - Bethlehem Church, Union County, 2001-2004 (Box RCD 148)
    - Bethlehem Church, Warren County, 1947-1948 (Box RCD 31)
    - Bethpage Church, Rowan County, 1947-1956 (Box RCD 31)
    - Beulah Church, Cleveland County, 1929-1930 (Box RCD 32)
    - Beulah Church, Sampson County, 1982-1983 (Box RCD 32)
    - Beulah Church, Surry County, 1958-1962 (Box RCD 32)
    - Beulah Church, Wilkes County, 1928-1929 (Box RCD 32)
    - Beulaville Church, Duplin County, 1964, 1972, 2 folders (Box RCD 32)
    - Big Cove Church, Swain County, 1955-1958 (Box RCD 32)
    - Big Spring Church, Mecklenburg County, 1945-1950 (Box RCD 32)
    - Black Creek Church, Wilson County, 1949-1972, 2 folders (Box RCD 32)
    - Black Mountain Church, Buncombe County, 1959-1969 (Box RCD 32)
    - Black Water Church, Surry County, 1955-1956 (Box RCD 32)
    - Blackburn's Chapel, Ashe County, 1949-1950 (Box RCD 32)
    - Black's Chapel, Cumberland County, 1925 (Box RCD 32)
    - Black's Chapel, Wayne County, 1961-1962 (Box RCD 32)
    - Bladen Springs Church, Bladen County, 1936-1938 (Box RCD 32)
    - Bladenboro Church, Bladen County, 1928-1938 (Box RCD 32)
    - Blair Road Church, Mecklenburg County, 1960, 1972-1974, 2 folders (Box RCD 32)
    - Boger's Chapel, Cabarrus County, 1938-1958 (Box RCD 32)
    - Boiling Springs Church, Cleveland County, 1958-1963, 1968-1974, 3 folders (Box RCD 32)
    - Bolton Church, Columbus County, 1928-1929 (Box RCD 32)
    - Bond's Grove Church, Union County, 1949-1970, 2 folders (Box RCD 32)
    - Boonville Church, Yadkin County, 1926-1931 (Box RCD 32)
    - Bridgeton Church, Craven County, 1952-1956 (Box RCD 33)
    - Bright Hope Laurel Church, Madison County, 1962-1963, 1982-1984, 3 folders (Box RCD 33)
    - Broad Creek Church, Carteret County, 1948-1955, 1973-1979, 2 folders (Box RCD 33)
    - Broadway Church, Lee County, 1922-1950, 1982-1984, 2 folders (Box RCD 33)
    - Brogden Church, Wayne County, 1959-1960 (Box RCD 33)
    - Brooks Chapel, Cleveland County, 1983-1984 (Box RCD 33)
    - Brooksdale Church, Person County, 1921-1963, 1988, 3 folders (Box RCD 33)
    - Brookland Church, Person County, 1954, (1987-1989, 2 folders (Box RCD 33)
    - Brookstown Church, Forsyth County, 1937-1959 (Box RCD 33)
    - Brower's Chapel, Randolph County, 1952-1958 (Box RCD 33)
    - Brown Summit, Guilford County, 1952-1969 (Box RCD 33)
    - Browning's Chapel, Sampson County, 1931-1944 (Box RCD 33)
    - Brown's Chapel, Chatham County, 1927-1945, 1979-1981, 2 folders (Box RCD 34)
    - Brown's View, Buncombe County, 1954-1955, 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box RCD 34)
    - Bryant Memorial Church, Surry County, 1958-1960 (Box RCD 34)
    - Bryson City Church, Swain County, 1958-1968 (Box RCD 34)
    - Bryson City Church, Swain County, 2000-2002, 2 folders (Box RCD 148)
    - Buckhorn Church, Chatham County, 1929-1941, 1986-1987, 2 folders (Box RCD 34)
    - Buckhorn Church, Wilson County, 1936-1951 (Box RCD 34)
    - Buie Church, Robeson County, 1937-1938 (Box RCD 34)
    - Bullock's Church, Granville County, 1927 (Box RCD 34)
    - Bunker Hill Church, Forsyth County, 1934-1974, 1984-1989, 4 folders (Box RCD 34)
    - Bunn Church, Franklin County, 1926-1928 (Box RCD 34)
    - Burgaw Church, Pender County, 1926-1982 (Box RCD 34)
    - Burke's Chapel, Burke County, 1952 (Box RCD 34)
    - Burnette's Chapel, Guilford County, 1957-1965, 1973-1977, 3 folders (Box RCD 34)
    - Butner Community Church, Granville County, 1964-1978, 2 folders (Box RCD 34)
    - Buxton Church, Dare County, 1928-1964, 2 folders (Box RCD 34)
    - Buxton Church, Dare County, 2002-2005 (Box RCD 148)
    - Caledonia Church, Scotland County, 1937, 1971-1974, 1985-1986, 3 folders (Box RCD 35)
    - Calvary Church, Halifax County, 1944-1947 (Box RCD 35)
    - Calvary Church, Johnston County, 1926-1933 (Box RCD 35)
    - Calvary Church, Randolph County, 1950-1960 (Box RCD 35)
    - Camden Church, Camden County, 1958-1962, 2 folders (Box RCD 35)
    - Camden Church, Camden County, 2002-2005 (Box RCD 148)
    - Cameron Church, Moore County, 1948-1950, 1976-1978, 2 folders (Box RCD 35)
    - Camp Church, Brunswick County,, 1982-1984 and undated, 2 folders (Box RCD 35)
    - Camp Ground Church, Cumberland County, 1952-1971, 2 folders (Box RCD 35)
    - Camp Springs Church, Caswell County, 1945-1949 (Box RCD 35)
    - Campbell's Creek Church, Beaufort County, 1927-1949 (Box RCD 35)
    - Canaan Church, Davidson County, 1942-1958, 1988-1990, 3 folders (Box RCD 35)
    - Candor Church, Montgomery County, 1927-1952, 1968-1975, 3 folders (Box RCD 36)
    - Carbonton Church, Chatham County, 1956-1967 (Box RCD 36)
    - Carbonton Church, Chatham County, 2003-2005 (Box RCD 148)
    - Caroleen Church, Rutherford County, 1966-1973 (Box RCD 36)
    - Carolina Beach Church, New Hanover County, 1946 (Box RCD 36)
    - Carroll's Chapel, Onslow County, 1957-1958 (Box RCD 36)
    - Carson Chapel, Macon County, 1943-1946 (Box RCD 36)
    - Carson's Chapel, Alexander County, 1947-1949 (Box RCD 36)
    - Carson's Chapel, McDowell County, 1950 (Box RCD 36)
    - Carthage Church, Moore County, 1938 (Box RCD 36)
    - Carver's Creek Church, Bladen County, 1945-1952, 1970, 2 folders (Box RCD 36)
    - Cary Church, Wake County, 1926-1928 (Box RCD 36)
    - Casar Church, Cleveland County, 1934-1958 (Box RCD 36)
    - Cashiers Church, Jackson County, 1925-1960, 1987-1989, 2 folders (Box RCD 36)
    - Castalia Church, Nash County, 1952-1955 (Box RCD 36)
    - Catawba Church, Catawba County, 1925-1948, 1992-1994, 2 folders (Box RCD 36)
    - Ca-Vel Church, Person County, 1940-1950 (Box RCD 36)
    - Cedar Cliff Church, Alamance County, 1948-1950, 1974-1978, 1986-1991, 3 folders (Box RCD 37)
    - Cedar Falls Church, Randolph County, 1941-1960 (Box RCD 37)
    - Cedar Grove Church, Chatham County, 1938-1961, 2 folders (Box RCD 37)
    - Cedar Grove Church, Orange County, 1934 (Box RCD 37)
    - Cedar Grove Church, Rutherford County, 1937 (Box RCD 37)
    - Cedar Grove Church, Stanly County, 1961-1962, 2 folders (Box RCD 37)
    - Cedar Grove Church, Tyrrell County, 1937-1938 (Box RCD 37)
    - Cedar Hill Church, Anson County, 1944-1967 (Box RCD 37)
    - Cedar Island Church, Carteret County, 1937-1956 (Box RCD 37)
    - Cedar Valley Church, Caldwell County, 1951-1952 (Box RCD 37)
    - Celia Phelps Church, Guilford County, 1973-1977 (Box RCD 37)
    - Celo Church, Yancey County, 1953-1955 (Box RCD 37)
    - Centenary Church, Davidson County, 1947-1962 (Box RCD 37)
    - Centenary Church, Davidson County, 1998-2004 (Box RCD 148)
    - Centenary Church, Rockingham County, 1979-1982 (Box RCD 37)
    - Centenary Church, Rowan County, 1926-1936, 1977-1981, 3 folders (Box RCD 37)
    - Centenary Church, Sampson County, 1951-1956 (Box RCD 37)
    - Centenary Church, Sampson County, 2001-2004 (Box RCD 148)
    - Center Church, Alexander County, 1932 (Box RCD 37)
    - Center Church, Bladen County, 1937-1938 (Box RCD 37)
    - Center Church, Cabarrus County, 1958-1959, 1967-1973, 2 folders (Box RCD 37)
    - Center Church, Catawba County, 1926-1961, 2 folders (Box RCD 38)
    - Center Church, Chatham County, 1948-1956 (Box RCD 38)
    - Center Church, Davidson County, 1925-1966, 1980-1983, 2 folders (Box RCD 38)
    - Center Church, Davie County, 1953-1954 (Box RCD 38)
    - Center Church, Guilford County, 1940-1945, 1976-1979, 1986-1989, 3 folders (Box RCD 38)
    - Center Church, Lee County, 1948-1950, 1979-1980, 2 folders (Box RCD 38)
    - Center Church, Union County, 1955-1957 (Box RCD 38)
    - Center Church, Yadkin County, 1948-1950 (Box RCD 38)
    - Center Grove Church, Cabarrus County, 1945-1973 (Box RCD 38)
    - Central Church, Ashe County, 1931-1932 (Box RCD 38)
    - Central Church, Haywood County, 1940-1951, 1978-1981, 2 folders (Box RCD 38)
    - Central Church, Scotland County, 1955-1959 (Box RCD 38)
    - Central Cross Church, Halifax County, 1925-1929 (Box RCD 38)
    - Central Falls Church, Randolph County, 1937-1941 (Box RCD 38)
    - Cerro Gordo Church, Columbus County, 1949-1951 (Box RCD 38)
    - Chapel Hill Church, Iredell County, 1930-1956, 1975-1980, Folder 1 of 2 (Box RCD 38)
    - Chapel Hill Church, Iredell County, 1930-1956, 1975-1980, Folder 2 of 2 (Box RCD 39)
    - Chapel Hill Church, Rockingham County, 1970 (Box RCD 39)
    - Chapel Oak Church, Swain County, 1929 (Box RCD 39)
    - Charity Church, Duplin County, 1945-1963 (Box RCD 39)
    - Charity Church, Wilkes County, North Wilkesboro District, 1941-1963, 2 folders (Box RCD 39)
    - Charity Church, Wilkes County, Winston-Salem District 1940-1951 (Box RCD 39)
    - Chase Church, Rutherford County, 1962-1963, 1973-1974, 2 folders (Box RCD 39)
    - Chatham Church, Chatham County, 1928-1960 (Box RCD 39)
    - Cherokee Church, Jackson County, 1951-1966 (Box RCD 39)
    - Cherry Point Church, Craven County, 1959-1970 (Box RCD 39)
    - Chestnut Grove Church, Davie County, 1961-1973, 3 folders (Box RCD 39)
    - Chestnut Grove Church, Stokes County, 1971-1974, 1980-1981, 2 folders (Box RCD 39)
    - Chestnut Hill Church, Ashe County, 1950 (Box RCD 39)
    - Chestnut Ridge Church, Orange County, 1954-1969, 1987-1989, 2 folders (Box RCD 39)
    - China Grove Church, Rowan County, 1926 (Box RCD 40)
    - Chocowinity, 1974 (Box RCD 40)
    - Christ Church, Alamance County, 1962, 1974, 2 folders (Box RCD 40)
    - Christ Church, Buncombe County, 1988-1990 (Box RCD 40)
    - Christ Church, Buncombe County, 2001-2004 (Box RCD 148)
    - Christ Church, Gaston County, 1985-1987 (Box RCD 40)
    - Christ Church, Mecklenburg County, 1960, 1971-1975, 2 folders (Box RCD 40)
    - Cid Church, Davidson County, 1944-1978, 2 folders (Box RCD 40)
    - Clark's Chapel, Buncombe County, 1958-1959, 1989, 2 folders (Box RCD 40)
    - Clark's Chapel, Macon County, 1927-1932 (Box RCD 40)
    - Clarks Church, Craven County, 1975-1977, 1982, 2 folders (Box RCD 40)
    - Clarks-Bethel Church, Dare County, 1940-1946 (Box RCD 40)
    - Clarksberry Church, Davidson County, 1931-1932 (Box RCD 41)
    - Clarksbury Church, Iredell County, 1932-1968, 1988, 2 folders (Box RCD 41)
    - Clarkton Church, Bladen County, 1948-1976, 2 folders (Box RCD 41)
    - Clear Springs Church, Davidson County, undated (Box RCD 41)
    - Clemmons Church, Forsyth County, 1940-1966, 1972-1981, 2 folders (Box RCD 41)
    - Cleveland Church, Rowan County, 1929-1965, 2 folders (Box RCD 41)
    - Clifton Church, Ashe County, 1952-1953 (Box RCD 41)
    - Clinchfield Church, McDowell County, 1987-1990 (Box RCD 41)
    - Clover Garden Church, Orange County, 1976-1980 (Box RCD 41)
    - Clover Hill Church, Cleveland County, 1935-1938 (Box RCD 41)
    - Coats Church, Harnett County, 1977 (Box RCD 41)
    - Cokesbury Church, Cumberland County, 1947-1954, 1987-1989, 2 folders (Box RCD 41)
    - Cokesbury Church, Harnett County, 1925-1942 (Box RCD 42)
    - Cokesbury Church, Mecklenburg County, 1958 (Box RCD 42)
    - Cokesbury Church, Vance County, 1926-1974 (Box RCD 42)
    - Cokesbury Church, Wake County, 1961 (Box RCD 42)
    - Cold Springs Church, Cabarrus County, 1937-1958 (Box RCD 42)
    - Cole Memorial Church, Mecklenburg County, 1939-1977 (Box RCD 42)
    - Colerain Church, Bertie County, 1939-1963, 2 folders (Box RCD 42)
    - Colington Church, Dare County, 1925-1927 (Box RCD 42)
    - Collier's Church, Caldwell County, 1960-1966, 2 folders (Box RCD 42)
    - Collin's Chapel, Robeson County, 1962-1969 (Box RCD 42)
    - Columbus Church, Polk County, 1962-1968, 2 folders (Box RCD 42)
    - Community Center Church, Robeson County, 1946-1950 (Box RCD 42)
    - Concord Church, Alamance County, 1944-1952, 1971, 2 folders (Box RCD 42)
    - Concord Church, Anson County, 1951-1953 (Box RCD 42)
    - Concord Church, Brunswick County, 1956 (Box RCD 42)
    - Concord Church, Catawba County, 1930-1945, 1971-1979, 2 folders (Box RCD 42)
    - Concord Church, Davie County, 1947-1954, 1979-1984, 3 folders (Box RCD 42)
    - Concord Church, Gaston County, 1934-1936, 1972-1973, 2 folders (Box RCD 43)
    - Concord Church, McDowell County, 1924-1927 (Box RCD 43)
    - Concord Church, Northampton County, 1935-1939 (Box RCD 43)
    - Concord Church, Person County, 1951 (Box RCD 43)
    - Concord Church, Randolph County, 1922-1938 (Box RCD 43)
    - Conetoe Church, Edgecombe County, 1925-1935 (Box RCD 43)
    - Connally Church, Caswell County, 1937 (Box RCD 43)
    - Connelly Springs Church, Burke County, 1931-1960 (Box RCD 43)
    - Conway Church, Northampton County, 1949-1978 (Box RCD 43)
    - Cool Springs Church, Harnett County, 1958-1960, 1973-1975, 2 folders (Box RCD 43)
    - Cool Springs Church, Iredell County, 1944-1957, 1970-1975, 3 folders (Box RCD 43)
    - Cool Springs Church, Moore County, 1932-1960 (Box RCD 43)
    - Cool Springs Church, Scotland County, 1932-1960 (Box RCD 43)
    - Cordova Church, Richmond County, 1980-1983 (Box RCD 43)
    - Corinth Church, Halifax County, 1941-1942 (Box RCD 43)
    - Cornatzer Church, Davie County, 1952-1970 (Box RCD 44)
    - Cotton Church, Cumberland County, 1952-1958, 1979-1980, 2 folders (Box RCD 44)
    - Cotton Grove Church, Davidson County, 1938-1940 (Box RCD 44)
    - Cox Chapel, Randolph County, 1977-1982 (Box RCD 44)
    - Crabtree Church, Haywood County, 1949-1950, 1981, 2 folders (Box RCD 44)
    - Creedmoor Church, Granville County, 1926-1959 (Box RCD 44)
    - Creswell Church, Washington County, 1933-1955 (Box RCD 44)
    - Crews Church, Forsyth County, 1943-1962, 2 folders (Box RCD 44)
    - Crouse Church, Lincoln County, 1936-1952 (Box RCD 44)
    - Crowell Memorial Church, Lincoln County, 1948-1950, 1973-1975, 1982-1983, 3 folders (Box RCD 44)
    - Cruso Church, Haywood County, 1959-1962, 1986-1988, 3 folders (Box RCD 44)
    - Culbreth Memorial Church, Cumberland County, 1941-1961, 1974-1983 1989-1990, Folder 1 of 3 (Box RCD 44)
    - Culbreth Memorial Church, Cumberland County, 1941-1961, 1974-1983 1989-1990, Folders 2-3 of 3 (Box RCD 45)
    - Cullowhee Church, Jackson County, 1935-1966, 2 folders (Box RCD 45)
    - Cullowhee Church, Jackson County, 2002-2005 (Box RCD 149)
    - Cumberland Church, Cumberland County, 1975-1977 (Box RCD 45)
    - Cumnock Church, Lee County, 1952 (Box RCD 45)
    - Cummings Memorial, Henderson County, 1989-1991 (Box RCD 45)
    - Currituck Church, Currituck County, 1926-1929 (Box RCD 45)
    - Dallas Church, Gaston County, 1925-1938 (Box RCD 45)
    - Dana Church, Henderson County, 1975-1976 (Box RCD 45)
    - Danbury Church, Stokes County, 1928-1933 (Box RCD 45)
    - Daniels Memorial Church, Wayne County, 1943-1965 (Box RCD 45)
    - David's Chapel, Lincoln County, 1946-1948 (Box RCD 45)
    - Deems Chapel, Bladen County, 1929-1930 (Box RCD 45)
    - Deerfield Church, Watauga County, 1960-1964, 1978-1982, 4 folders (Box RCD 46)
    - Dellwood Church, Haywood County, 1949-1957 (Box RCD 46)
    - Delta Church, Stokes County, 1945-1948 (Box RCD 46)
    - Denton Church, Davidson County, 1934-1964, 2 folders (Box RCD 46)
    - Denton Central Church, Davidson County, 1962-1964, 1977-1982, 3 folders (Box RCD 46)
    - Denton's Chapel, Burke County, 1962-1970 (Box RCD 46)
    - Denver Church, Lincoln County, 1945-1955, 1978-1982, 2 folders (Box RCD 46)
    - Derita Church, Mecklenburg County, 1933-1950 (Box RCD 46)
    - Deyton Bend Church, Yancey County, 1934-1943 (Box RCD 46)
    - Dix Creek Church, Buncombe County, 1954 (Box RCD 46)
    - Dixon's Chapel, Brunswick County, 1938-1978, 2 folders (Box RCD 46)
    - Dobson Church, Surry County, 1926-1969, 2 folders (Box RCD 46)
    - Double Shoals Church, Cleveland County, 1935-1936 (Box RCD 47)
    - Doubs Chapel, Forsyth County, 1950-1959 (Box RCD 47)
    - Doubs Chapel, Moore County, 1958 (Box RCD 47)
    - Dover Church, Craven County, 1957 (Box RCD 47)
    - Drewry Church, Vance County, 1933-1934 (Box RCD 47)
    - Drexel: Christ Church, Burke County, 1977-1989, 3 folders (Box RCD 47)
    - Dryman's Chapel, Macon County, 1953-1954 (Box RCD 47)
    - Duck Church, Dare County, 1975-1976 (Box RCD 47)
    - Duke's Chapel, Durham County, 1926-1969 (Box RCD 47)
    - Duke Divinity School, Durham County, 2003-2004 (Box RCD 149)
    - Dulins Church, Davie County, 1954-1955, 1972-1975, 2 folders (Box RCD 47)
    - Dunkirk Church, Wilkes County, 1957-1962, 2 folders (Box RCD 47)
    - Eagle Falls Church, Rockingham County, 1955-1956 (Box RCD 47)
    - East Bend Church, Yadkin County, 1956-1974 (Box RCD 47)
    - East End Church, Gaston County, 1945-1949 (Box RCD 47)
    - East Flat Rock Church, Henderson County, 1941-1951, 1977-1980, 1985-1988, 3 folders (Box RCD 47)
    - East Rockingham Church, Richmond County, 1948, 1980-1983, 2 folders (Box RCD 48)
    - Ebenezer Church, Caldwell County, 1931-1966, 1978-1983, 3 folders (Box RCD 48)
    - Ebenezer Church, Catawba County, 1941-1959, 1975-1981, 2 folders (Box RCD 48)
    - Ebenezer Church, Davidson County, 1941-1959, 1984-1986, 2 folders (Box RCD 48)
    - Ebenezer Church, Gaston County, 1927-1953 (Box RCD 48)
    - Ebenezer Church, Halifax County, 1941-1950 (Box RCD 48)
    - Ebenezer Church, Johnston County, 1929 (Box RCD 48)
    - Ebenezer Church, Lincoln County, 1988-1992 (Box RCD 48)
    - Ebenezer Church, McDowell County, 1950-1962 (Box RCD 48)
    - Ebenezer Church, Rowan County, 1932-1968 (Box RCD 48)
    - Ebenezer Church, Surry County, 1 9540-1954 (Box RCD 48)
    - Ebenezer Church, Wake County, 1961-1966 (Box RCD 48)
    - Ebenezer Church, Wayne County, 1955-1980, 1986-1987, 2 folders (Box RCD 49)
    - Eden Church, Rockingham County, 1929-1968 (Box RCD 49)
    - Edneyville Church, Henderson County, 1934-1944, 1971-1975, 2 folders (Box RCD 49)
    - Edward's Chapel, Lenoir County, 1952-1953 (Box RCD 49)
    - El Bethel Church, Randolph County, 1928-1969 (Box RCD 49)
    - Elbaville Church, Davie County, 1953-1956, 1973-1975, 2 folders (Box RCD 49)
    - Eleazer Church, Randolph County, 1951-1954 (Box RCD 49)
    - Elevation Church, Johnston County, 1947-1948 (Box RCD 49)
    - Elizabeth Chapel, Haywood County, 1956-1968 (Box RCD 49)
    - Elizabeth Church, Johnston County, 1935-1957 (Box RCD 49)
    - Elk Park Church, Avery County, 1950 (Box RCD 49)
    - Elkwood Church, Buncombe County, 1947-1948 (Box RCD 49)
    - Ellerbe Church, Richmond County, 1952-1955 (Box RCD 49)
    - Ellis Church, Durham County, 1930-1931 (Box RCD 49)
    - Elm City Church, Wilson County, 1928-1933, 1975-1977, 2 folders (Box RCD 49)
    - Elm Grove Church, Forsyth County, 1948-1950, 1965-1967, 2 folders (Box RCD 50)
    - Elmwood Church, Iredell County, 1921-1953 (Box RCD 50)
    - Emma Church, Buncombe County, 1963-1964, 1979-1981, 3 folders (Box RCD 50)
    - Englehard Church, Hyde County, 1926-1961 (Box RCD 50)
    - English Chapel, Transylvania County, 1940-1957 (Box RCD 50)
    - Eno Church, Orange County, 1957-1959 (Box RCD 50)
    - Epworth Church, Cabarrus County, 1958-1961, 2 folders (Box RCD 50)
    - Epworth Church, Craven County, 1934-1968 (Box RCD 50)
    - Epworth Church, Mecklenburg County, 1958 (Box RCD 50)
    - Epworth Church, Sampson County, 1940-1976, 1982-1991, 4 folders (Box RCD 50)
    - Eschol Church, Wilkes County, 1958-1959 (Box RCD 50)
    - Etowah Church, Henderson County, 1957-1965, 1983-1987, 3 folders (Box RCD 50)
    - Eureka Church, Wayne County, 1938-1941 (Box RCD 50)
    - Evansdale Church, Wilson County, 1941 (Box RCD 51)
    - Evergreen Church, Columbus County, 1927-1954 (Box RCD 51)
    - Fair Bluff Church, Columbus County, 1935 (Box RCD 51)
    - Fair Grove Church, Catawba County, 1928-1935 (Box RCD 51)
    - Fair Grove Church, Rockingham County, 1964-1969 (Box RCD 51)
    - Fair Haven Church, Dare County, 1943-1973 (Box RCD 51)
    - Fair Promise Church, Moore County, 1958-1959 (Box RCD 51)
    - Fair View Church, Iredell County, 1959-1964 (Box RCD 51)
    - Fairfield Church, Guilford County, 1961-1965, 1986-1991, 2 folders (Box RCD 51)
    - Fairfield Church, Lincoln County, 1984-1986 (Box RCD 51)
    - Fairgrove Church, Catawba County, 1958-1961, 1969-1973, 3 folders (Box RCD 51)
    - Fairgrove Church, Davidson County, 1936-1937 (Box RCD 51)
    - Fairmont Church, Iredell County, 1953-1957 (Box RCD 51)
    - Fairview Church, Alamance County, 1950-1955 (Box RCD 51)
    - Fairview Church, Davidson County, Cid Charge, 1942-1945, 1972-1980, 2 folders (Box RCD 51)
    - Fairview Church, Davidson County, Pinewood-Fairview Charge 1942-1974, 4 folders (Box RCD 51)
    - Fairview Church, Iredell County, 1962 (Box RCD 51)
    - Fairview Church, Madison County, 1925-1927 (Box RCD 51)
    - Fairview Church, Randolph County, 1960-1969 (Box RCD 52)
    - Fairview Church, Surry County, 1973-1975 (Box RCD 52)
    - Fairview-Sharon Church, Buncombe County, 1966-1973 (Box RCD 52)
    - Faison Church, Duplin County, 1960-1966, 1977-1979, 3 folders (Box RCD 52)
    - Faith Church, Alamance County, 1946-1949 (Box RCD 52)
    - Faith Church, Craven County, 1986-1988 (Box RCD 52)
    - Falling Creek Church, Wayne County, 1934-1961, 2 folders (Box RCD 52)
    - Fanning's Chapel, Henderson County, 1962-1963, 1971, 2 folders (Box RCD 52)
    - Farmington Church, Davie County, 1988-1990 (Box RCD 52)
    - Federal Point Church, New Hanover County, 1941-1942 (Box RCD 52)
    - Fellowship Church, Johnston County, 1936-1965, 2 folders (Box RCD 52)
    - Fincher's Chapel, Haywood County, 1948-1949, 1990, 2 folders (Box RCD 52)
    - Fines Creek Church, Haywood County, 1952-1955 (Box RCD 52)
    - First Liberty Church, Randolph County, 1952-1955 (Box RCD 52)
    - First Methodist Church, Montgomery County, 1958-1972, 2 folders (Box RCD 53)
    - First Methodist Church, Robeson County, 1957-1966 (Box RCD 53)
    - Flag Springs Church, Randolph County, 1954-1968, 1976-1980, 3 folders (Box RCD 53)
    - Flat Rock Church, Guilford County, 1962-1965, 2 folders (Box RCD 53)
    - Flat Rock Church, Vance County, 1950-1955, 1979-1982, 2 folders (Box RCD 53)
    - Fletcher Chapel, Henderson County, 1926-1928, 1971-1972, 2 folders (Box RCD 53)
    - Fletcher's Chapel, Durham County, 1921-1966, 2 folders (Box RCD 53)
    - Forest Chapel Church, Stokes County, 1939-1964 (Box RCD 53)
    - Forestville Church, Anson County, 1926-1960 (Box RCD 53)